<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Femboy Bee</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Femboy Bee</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:06:27 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Bee Acquires a Drawing Tablet</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/drawing-tablet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:06:27 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/drawing-tablet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A week ago, I got a new drawing tablet! It&amp;rsquo;s a ugee Q6, meant for mobile phones, but im using it for my laptop instead. For some reason the drawing area isn&amp;rsquo;t working properly for my phone, but thats fine, because it works nicely on my laptop! I felt like being able to draw freely as soon as I got the drawing tablet&amp;hellip; Also finally having the opportunity to escape ibisPaint and learn on using Krita!! Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to start making new drawings with it&amp;hellip; I did already doodle with it a lot!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination Sucks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 17:34:02 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Screw you procrastination! God, you really held me back for so long on making my website- ahem. Anyways! Yayyy I finally have my own website &amp;gt;w&amp;lt;!! Getting off &lt;a href=&#34;https://straw.page&#34;&gt;straw.page&lt;/a&gt; now as im able to get more customizations and stuff! Though this isn&amp;rsquo;t the most for now, im tired lol. The straw.page may be taken down at some point but im lazy to update it right now. The stuff I host is also in here so yeye! Thanks to Linerly for motivating me enough to finally make my own website! This stuff is powered by Hugo btw, a static site generator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
